[{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980212763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":9555,"timeElapsed":62923},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980218963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6199,"timeElapsed":69123},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980228754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9790,"timeElapsed":78914},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980235210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":6454,"timeElapsed":85370},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980242250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7039,"timeElapsed":92410},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980246555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4304,"timeElapsed":96715},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980253146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":6590,"timeElapsed":103306},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980259500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6352,"timeElapsed":109659},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980266690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":7189,"timeElapsed":116850},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980282204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":13871,"timeElapsed":132363},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980287467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5262,"timeElapsed":137627},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3254,"timeElapsed":140882},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980293675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2952,"timeElapsed":143835},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980296635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2960,"timeElapsed":146795},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980299538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2901,"timeElapsed":149698},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980302219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":152378},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4408,"timeElapsed":156788},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":159522},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980319659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":9047,"timeElapsed":169819},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3048,"timeElapsed":172868},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5518,"timeElapsed":178386},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":181012},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980333538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2686,"timeElapsed":183698},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980336282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2743,"timeElapsed":186442},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2527,"timeElapsed":188970},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4055,"timeElapsed":193026},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4151,"timeElapsed":197179},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980358362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10070,"timeElapsed":208522},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5305,"timeElapsed":213828},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":6277,"timeElapsed":220107},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2896,"timeElapsed":223004},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377107,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4262,"timeElapsed":227267},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3303,"timeElapsed":230571},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980383339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2927,"timeElapsed":233499},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2352,"timeElapsed":235852},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8478,"timeElapsed":244331},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3648,"timeElapsed":247980},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":9864,"timeElapsed":258860},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2494,"timeElapsed":261355},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980414947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3751,"timeElapsed":265107},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2327,"timeElapsed":267435},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2567,"timeElapsed":270004},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980422243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2398,"timeElapsed":272403},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1943,"timeElapsed":274347},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2767,"timeElapsed":277115},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2103,"timeElapsed":279219},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":11736,"timeElapsed":291876},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980443685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1967,"timeElapsed":293844},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2431,"timeElapsed":296277},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1943,"timeElapsed":298220},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":300940},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2495,"timeElapsed":303436},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2398,"timeElapsed":305836},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5942,"timeElapsed":311779},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2559,"timeElapsed":314339},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12215,"timeElapsed":327603},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980479052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1607,"timeElapsed":329212},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980481444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":331604},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1903,"timeElapsed":333508},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980485660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2311,"timeElapsed":335820},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":338107},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2297,"timeElapsed":340405},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493668,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3421,"timeElapsed":343827},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4543,"timeElapsed":348372},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2223,"timeElapsed":350595},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9936,"timeElapsed":361821},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980513636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1974,"timeElapsed":363796},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2464,"timeElapsed":366261},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2805,"timeElapsed":369067},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4329,"timeElapsed":373397},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2127,"timeElapsed":375525},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2087,"timeElapsed":377613},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2966,"timeElapsed":380580},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980532804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":382964},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5944,"timeElapsed":390021},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2071,"timeElapsed":392094},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2413,"timeElapsed":394508},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2185,"timeElapsed":396693},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2566,"timeElapsed":399261},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2318,"timeElapsed":401580},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3407,"timeElapsed":404988},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2560,"timeElapsed":407549},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1838,"timeElapsed":409388},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6478,"timeElapsed":416781},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2350,"timeElapsed":419132},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4824,"timeElapsed":423957},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2519,"timeElapsed":426477},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2142,"timeElapsed":428620},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3096,"timeElapsed":431717},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1909,"timeElapsed":433628},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2400,"timeElapsed":436029},{"subjectID":"maf0btxqej","prolificID":"6742608322d0083c8b374bb2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22b16991c1b08a5721e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":1870,"timeElapsed":437900}]